http://www.bookcrossing.com/privacy

Privacy Policy
BookCrossing respects and protects the privacy of the individuals that use the BookCrossing.com site. Individually
identifiable information about you is not willfully disclosed to any third party without first receiving your permission,
as explained in this privacy policy.
Children under the age of 13
When someone under the age of 13 attempts to register with BookCrossing, we ask that he or she have a parent, teacher or librarian establish a BookCrossing Account for them. When any user registers for a BookCrossing account, we require first name, email address, birth date, city, state/province, country, and zip code. BookCrossing uses this information to create and maintain accounts, for research, and may use this information to customize the content seen on our pages. Under the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, no web site operator can require, as a condition of participation in an activity, that a child under the age of 13 disclose more information than is reasonably necessary. BookCrossing abides by this requirement.
BookCrossing and Cookies
Upon your first visit to BookCrossing, BookCrossing sends a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a piece of data that
identifies you as a unique member. BookCrossing uses cookies to improve the quality of our service. BookCrossing does this
by storing member preferences in cookies. BookCrossing will not disclose its cookies to third parties. Most browsers are
initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is
being sent. Be aware, however, that some parts of BookCrossing may not function properly if you refuse cookies.
What Information Do We Collect?
BookCrossing does not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when
you specifically and knowingly provide such information on your member profile page.
Links to Other Sites
The sites linked to by BookCrossing are developed by people over whom BookCrossing exercises no control. These other
sites may send their own cookies to members, collect data, or solicit personal information.
With Whom Does BookCrossing Share Information?
BookCrossing does not share your personal membership information with any other company, individual, or organization.
We do not and will not "sell" our member data to any advertisers, and nobody except us will ever contact you based on the
information you provide to us. Note that your Member Profile page has two important options: your Newsletter
preference, and your Allow Members to Contact You Anonymously option. You can turn these on or off
at any time.
Your consent and changes to the Privacy Policy
By using the BookCrossing site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in
this policy. BookCrossing may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will notify all
our members by email so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what
circumstances we disclose it.
Referral Program
When you use the BookCrossing referral program (the "Referral Program"), we may ask you to provide information such
as your email address and your friends' email addresses. In return, you and your friends will be given the opportunity
to register with BookCrossing, and your friends will also be given the opportunity to make referrals to their friends.
This feature helps us spread the word about BookCrossing. During and after participation in the Referral Program you
and/or your friends may receive additional communications from us or our vendors in relation to the Referral Program
and you and/or your friends' participation in it. The data collected through the Referral Program is only used for
the operation and ongoing maintenance of the Referral Program and will not be distributed to any third parties other
than those BookCrossing trusted partners that may be helping us in the operation and maintenance of the Referral
Program.
You and your friends may opt-out of participation in the Referral Program at any time via opt-out links
in all communications made to you and your friends through the Referral Program or by sending an email to
members_optout@BookCrossing.com.
What can I do if I have additional questions?
Feel free to contact us any time and we'll answer any additional questions you may have.
Terms and Services
BookPlate Creator
If you click the box "Make My Bookplate Public" you are agreeing to the Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions:
You hereby grant BookCrossing an perpetual, irrevocable, non-exclusive, transferable, fully paid, global license to use, copy, publish, stream, store, retain, publicly perform or display, transmit, scan, reformat, modify, edit, frame, translate, excerpt, adapt, create derivative works and distribute, any photos, images or content you upload.
You may remove your photo from the Site at any time but if another user has placed an order and paid while using your photo, the order will be processed and reproduced.
The license granted above will automatically expire, however you acknowledge that any orders placed before you remove your photo will be processed.
You are responsible for all of the images you upload to our site. You must have the legal right to copy and display each image that you upload, share or print. You should assume that all text, graphics and images that you find on the World Wide Web are subject to a copyright. In general, it is a violation of federal law to copy text, graphics or images that are subject to a copyright and use the copyrighted material on custom products created using this service without the consent of the owner of the copyright. Before copying any text, graphics or images, you must confirm that it is in the public domain and not subject to a copyright or obtain the consent of the owner of the copyright to use the material. You authorize BookCrossing.com to cooperate with copyright owners who claim that you have infringed or may infringe their intellectual property rights. This cooperation includes, but is not limited to taking the following action without notice: disclosing your material and any other information you have disclosed to us to the copyright owner or its agent and destroying all alleged infringing material. BookCrossing.com may also suspend or terminate the account of a customer who appears to be infringing Intellectual Property, and may take further appropriate action.
The fact that we produce the custom bookplate does not mean that: (1) we approve or endorse the content of the custom bookplate, (2) the custom bookplate complies with all applicable laws, or (3) you will not incur any liability or harm arising from the custom bookplate.
Furthermore, you agree to refrain from using the BookCrossing.com services, your customized bookplates, or images of your customized bookplates in any manner that would cause damage to the public reputation of BookCrossing.com, its employees, shareholders, board members, or partners. In the event that you use or publicly display your customized bookplate, including by display on the Internet, in order to intentionally bring harm to BookCrossing.com, its employees, shareholders, board members or partners, BookCrossing.com reserves the right to demand the immediate return of your customized products.
Recently Released
Recently Caught
Track Random Acts of Kindness
Check out ButterflyCoins.org, another project from the BookCrossing team!
Bookish Quotes
"The books that the world calls immoral are the books that show the world its own shame."
Round 9 of Support BC - Supply Store Sweepstakes is here!
News from the Store: Vacation time
see all...
Are you sure you want to delete this item? It cannot be undone.
